{
    "question": "buatkan Naskah drama bahasa inggris untuk 7 orang. cewek 4 orang, cwok 3 orang....\r\ntolong :)\u00a0 bebas, tpi jangan pnjng.panjang",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "Kiki: Hello,Good Morning all\nTerusin Aja yah Tema nasjah englus itu yg bagus best friend in my heart",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "buatlah-dialog-expression-of-plan-804",
            "question": "Buatlah dialog expression of plan...",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Nancy :hai, Nan....<br>Arum : hai,,,<br>Nancy : Rum, I have a plan to our class in this holiday,<br>Arum : hmmm, what?<br>Nancy : We will go to Amri&#039;s home, his home at highlands, how? are you agree with me?<br>Arum : I agree, we must tell our classmate ,,,<br>Nancy : Yes, when?<br>Arum : faster is better<br>Nancy : yeh...<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "apakah-artinya-lapangan-sepak-bola-dalam-bahasa-inggris-313",
            "question": "Apakah artinya lapangan sepak bola dalam bahasa inggris",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<span>football field</span> jawabanya<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "football field : lapangan sepak bola",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "contoh-kalimat-active-passive-pada-present-simple-past-simple-p-261",
            "question": "Contoh kalimat active passive pada present simple, past simple, present cont, dan past cont!:)",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Simple Present Tense<br>\u00a0-Active : I\ncall my best friend<br>\u00a0-Passive :\nI am called by my best friend<br>Simple Past Tense<br>\u00a0-Active : I\ncalled my friend yesterday\n<br>\n-Passive :\nI was called by my best friend yesterday\n\n<br>Present\nContinous Tense<br>\u00a0-Active : I\nam calling my best friend<br>\u00a0-Passive :\nI am being called by my best friend<br>\u00a0Past\nContinous Tense<br>\u00a0-Active : I\nwas calling my best friend<br>\u00a0-Passive :\nI was being called by my best friend\n\n<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "jelaskan-dan-berikan-contoh-verbnounadjectiveand-adverbs-933",
            "question": "Jelaskan dan berikan contoh verb,noun,adjective,and adverbs",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<span><span>\"Joe ate his\u00a0banana.\"</span>\u00a0-\u00a0noun</span><span><span>\"They\u00a0ran\u00a0all the way home.\"</span>\u00a0-\u00a0verb</span><span><span>\"You are a\u00a0pretty\u00a0girl.\"</span>\u00a0-\u00a0adjective</span><span><span>\"He\u00a0quietly\u00a0opened the door.\"</span>\u00a0-\u00a0<span>adverb</span></span>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "verb : kata kerja contoh : sitdown,stand up,laughing<br>noun : kata benda conntoh : chair,pencilcase<br>adverb : kata keterangan contoh : now,yesterday,tomorrow<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "buat-karangan-3-paragraf-tentang-profesi-guru-dlm-bahasa-inggris-159",
            "question": "Buat karangan 3 paragraf tentang profesi guru dlm bahasa inggris",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<strong>Why God Made TeachersBy Kevin William Huff</strong><br>When God created teachers,\u00a0He gave us special friends\u00a0To help us understand His world\u00a0And truly comprehend\u00a0The beauty and the wonder\u00a0Of everything we see,\u00a0And become a better person\u00a0With each discovery.\u00a0<br>When God created teachers,\u00a0He gave us special guides\u00a0To show us ways in which to grow\u00a0So we can all decide\u00a0How to live and how to do\u00a0What&#039;s right instead of wrong,\u00a0To lead us so that we can lead\u00a0And learn how to be strong.\u00a0<br>Why God created teachers,\u00a0In His wisdom and His grace,\u00a0Was to help us learn to make our world\u00a0<span>A better, wiser place.</span>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "apa-arti-nya-i-like-this-461",
            "question": "Apa arti nya i like this",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "\u00a0i like this artimya\u00a0aku suka ini \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Saya suka ini :D<br>gampang sekali<br><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "descripition-text-about-museum-fatahillah-3-paraghraphs-106",
            "question": "Descripition text about museum fatahillah (3 paraghraphs)",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "The Jakarta history museum, also known as<em> Fatahillah Museum</em> or <em>Batavia Museum,</em> is located in the Old Town, Jakarta City, Indonesia. The building was built in 1710 as the <em>Stadhuis (city hal) </em>of batavia . It&#039;s opened in 1974. This building was the administrative headquarters of the <strong>Dutch East India Company and </strong>later of the<strong> Dutch Government. </strong>The current building was constructed in 1707 by the city government.<br><strong><br></strong>The building resembles the Dam place in Amsterdam, consist of a main building with two wings on the east and west\u00a0as well as sanding building used as offices, court rooms, and underground spaces are used as a prison. Facilities are library, diner museum, souvenir shop, cinema fatahilah, mosque, etc<br><strong><br></strong>Ativity. from 2001-2002 the jakarta history museum of arts program held every week nusantara II and IV for all 2003 jakarta history museum. This event focuses on the nuances of betawi art<strong><br><br><br><br></strong>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "ada-yang-bisa-kasi-masukan-judul-fairy-tale-legenda-dan-fabel-916",
            "question": "ada yang bisa kasi masukan judul fairy tale, legenda, dan fabel? masing - masing 5 kakak :\"D Terimakasih",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "menurut aku....<br>fairy tale: pinnochio, cinderella, alice in the wonderland(rada fabel dikit ini ), tinkerbell,snow white, frozen, the little mermaid, dll princess2 gitu deh bisa disebut fairy tale<br>legenda: malin kundang, dsb lah yg gituan pkonya<br>fabel: si kancil, bugs bunny, tom and jerry, dll yang pokonya ttg binatang yang bisa berbicara seperti manusia:)<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Fiary Tale : The Prince of Frog, Cinderella, Beauty and The Beast, Sleeping Beauty, Snow White<br>Legenda :\u00a0 Malin Kundang, Sangkuriang, Roro Jonggrang, Lake Toba, Kang Kabayan<br>Fabel : Kancil and The Giant Story, The King Kinka, Kancil and The Tiger, Kancil and Crocodile, The Rock and The Weasel<br>Semoga membantu ^_^<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "contoh-kalimat-active-passive-pd-present-perfect-past-perfect-f-733",
            "question": "Contoh kalimat active passive pd present perfect, past perfect, future present, future past!:)",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Present\nPerfect Tense\n<br>\n- Active : I\nhave called my best friend<br>- Passive :\nI have been called by my best friend\n\n<br>Past\nPerfect Tense<br>- Active : I\nhad called my best friend\n<br>\n- Passive :\nI had been called by my best friend\n<br>\nSimple\nFuture Tense<br>- Active : I\nshall call my best friend\n<br>\n- Passive :\nI shall be call by called by my best friend<br>\u00a0Future Past\nTense<br>\u00a0- Active : I\nshould call my best friend<br>\u00a0- Passive :\nI should be called by my best friend\n\n<br><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "buat-kalimat-dari-kata-punishment-945",
            "question": "Buat kalimat dari kata punishment",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "the teacher gave punishment to the students who didn&#039;t do homework<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<span>criminals were punishment because they stole goods belonging to <span>citizens</span></span>.<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}